<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CVS_FalkirkFundersFayre2019</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="home_legal">www.cvsfalkirk.org.uk | 01324 692000 | info@cvsfalkirk.org.uk | @CVSFalkirk
        \nCVS Falkirk and District is a Company Limited by Guarantee in Scotland No. SC085838 | Scottish Charity No. SC000312 |
        Registered office: Unit 6, Callendar Business Park, Callendar Road, Falkirk, FK1 1XR</string>

    <string name="home_p1">Thank you for coming along to our Funders Fayre today, we hope you find the event useful and informative. CVS Falkirk and Falkirk Council
    work together to support local third sector organisations to access funding and are grateful to all our exhibitors here today.\n
    </string>

    <string name="home_p2">As the Third Sector Interface for the Falkirk Council area, CVS Falkirk exists to
    promote, develop and represent the third sector and volunteering. We offer
    assistance and support to communities, groups, voluntary organisations, social enterprises, co-operatives, trusts, CICs and other third sector groups locally.\n
    </string>

    <string name="home_p3">Within the organisation support team we offer funding support and guidance to third sector organisations through a variety of ways:
    </string>

    <string name="home_list">
        \n• Bespoke funding search specific to the organisation and project
        \n• Support to understand funders’ guidance, criteria etc.
        \n• Review of funding applications
        \n• Weekly funding updates through our e-bulletin
        \n• Monthly funding hotlists
        \n• Promotion of local fundraising events through our website,
        \n• e-bulletin and social media

    </string>
    <string name="home_contact">test</string>
    <string name="home_signup">test</string>
    <string name="home_heading">Welcome\n</string>

</resources>
